Ah… I can indeed see something
啊 我的確能看到
like skeletons beside the window.
窗邊有某種類似骸骨的東西
Although they are hidden in the smoke,
雖然隱藏在煙霧之中
we can vaguely see huge bones.
但我們隱約可以看到巨大的骨頭
As far as the result is concerned,
雖說就結果而言
the fact that the children were saved is the greatest blessing.
孩子們得救了就是最大的幸事
Wow, amazing!
好厲害好厲害
Something like this actually happened yesterday.
昨天居然發生了這種事
Monsters really do exist!
原來怪物真的存在啊
Yeah.
就是說啊
I didn't expect that this kind of thing would actually happen around me.
沒想到這種事會發生在我的身邊
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《屍體如山的死亡遊戲》
Misaki,
我說 美咲
are you really okay
妳跟殺死自己的傢伙待在一起
to be with the person who killed you?
真的沒問題嗎
I was killed for the first time
我還是第一次被殺掉
and I feel so excited,
感覺好興奮啊
so there's no problem.
所以這樣是沒問題的
Right, you were
說得也是 妳的腦袋
never quite normal.
本來就不太正常
By the way,
話說回來
is Clarissa
這幢大樓的持有者
also the owner of this building?
也是克拉麗莎嗎
Well…
那個
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
我很抱歉給你們添了這麼多麻煩
Thank you very much for your help.
我十分感謝你們的幫助
To be honest, I know almost
老實說 我對這邊的世界
nothing about this world.
幾乎一無所知
Don't thank me.
你先別道謝了
Are you really planning to stay here?
你真的打算住在這裡嗎
SHAKUZAWA BUILDING
(拷問大樓)
Although you were reincarnated,
雖然你是轉生而來的
that the owner of this body still has a family,
但你的那具身體是有家人的吧
so how are you going to handle it?
你打算要怎麼處理啊
The owner of this body seems to be on summer vacation now.
這具身體的主人現在貌似在放暑假
I told Polka Shinoyama's family that
我告訴四乃山波爾卡的家人
I embarked on a journey to find myself, which was just an excuse.
說我踏上了尋找自我的旅程 總算是把他們給糊弄過去了
Clarissa said
克拉麗莎說
Isn't this a scam to confuse people about the death time?
這不就是混淆死亡時間的騙術嗎
But what should I do after summer vacation is over?
可是等暑假過去後 我該怎麼辦呢
For those family members,
關於家裡人的情況
I only know their names.
我僅僅是知道他們的名字而已
Can't you extract it from your brain
你沒法從腦袋裡 提取出關於他們的事情嗎
like the memory or something like that?
像是回憶什麼的
Language is something
因為語言之類的東西
due to repeated use,
所以我才能簡單地提取出來
while retrieving memories is as difficult as going back in time.
而提取回憶則像是回到過去一樣困難
Moreover,
而且
the impression left by recent memory is too strong.
最後那段記憶給我留下的印象 實在是太過強烈了
However, speaking of the other world,
不過話說回來 你之前待的地方是異世界啊
after seeing those bone monsters,
當我看到那種骨頭怪物之後
I couldn't help but believe it.
我也只能相信真的有異世界存在了
But we still can't say for sure
我現在還不能斷言
After all, there are similar things that exist in both worlds.
畢竟兩個世界存在類似的地方
For example, this creature is called a whale.
比方說 這種名為鯨魚的生物
In my world,
我那邊的世界裡將其記錄為
it is recorded as a legendary beast.
傳說中的幻獸
But what's important to me
但對我來說 最重要的是
is whether the Geldwood Church
這邊的世界裡 是否存在蓋爾德伍德教團
Geld… What?
你說蓋爾德什麼
They are a group of people
那是將我視為邪惡之物
who see me as an evil creature and plan to eliminate me.
打算消滅我的一幫人
In my original world,
我在原本的世界裡
Ah… that one.
啊 原來你就是那個怪物啊
What is your name in that world?
你在原本的世界裡叫什麼名字
In the language of this country,
我想想 用這個國家的語言來說的話 我的名字叫做…
it should be called "Dead Body Shrine."
屍體神社…不對
No, it should be "Corpse God."
我的名字應該是“屍神殿”
Corpse God... What a cool name!
屍神殿 這個名字好酷
Is that so?
這名字哪裡酷了
I am finally
我總算有可能過上安穩的生活了
The only thing left to do
去說服想要殺掉這具身體的
Let me say this first,
我話先說在前頭
Did you not ask Clarissa about it?
你沒能從克拉麗莎的嘴裡 問出雇主是誰嗎
I asked.
是的
But she insisted on her obligation to keep confidential.
她執意堅守保密義務 作為交換
In exchange, she waived my rent for this floor.
她免去了我這層樓的房租
After all, using force to discover the other party's identity
畢竟靠力量來問出對方的身分
is my last resort.
是我最後的手段
First of all, I have to do something on my own.
我打算先靠自己的力量去做些什麼
Clarissa also said that
克拉麗莎還跟我說
she will not accept any more commissions to kill me in the future.
她今後不會再承接殺我的委託
You believe everything she says?
她說什麼你都信啊
There are not only Sis Clarissa
從事殺手仲介的
as a middleman for assassins.
可不只有克拉麗莎大姐喔
However, there should be very few people
不過 能夠將你這種
with exceptional strength.
應該寥寥無幾吧
But if it is Lemmings, that would be possible.
不過“旅鼠軍團”的話 倒是有可能會把你給殺掉
Lammin?
呂樹君團？
Ah… let's not worry about it for now.
啊 那個 你先不用管這個東西
Speaking of which…
話說回來
Hey, hey, this is really amazing.
喂喂 這個好厲害啊
How does it move?
它是怎麼動起來的啊
Does it rely on button batteries?
它是靠鈕扣電池動起來的嗎？
Are you really okay
你和殺掉自己的美咲待在一起
After all, it's not me who was killed.
畢竟被殺掉的人又不是我
Is it really a good idea
你讓那種危險的傢伙復活
No problem, because the owner of this body,
無妨 既然這具身體的主人
Polka,
波爾卡他本人都說要原諒她了
I don't think there's anything wrong with it.
我覺得把她復活應該是沒什麼不行的
Have you talked
難道說 你和波爾卡的靈魂
to Polka's soul?
說過話了嗎
What do you mean by talk? He is right there.
什麼說不說話的 他本人就在那裡啊
It is my drone that couldn't be
原來是我昨天無法操縱的那架
controlled yesterday.
無人機啊
Polka's soul
因為波爾卡的靈魂
still lingers in this body,
仍然殘留在這具身體裡
so I transferred it into something nearby.
所以我就讓他附在了附近的東西上
Can it borrow your drone
在找到新的附身對象之前
until a new host is found?
可以讓他借用一下你的無人機嗎
Well…
那個
Put that aside first.
先不談借不借無人機給他 你…
You treat people's souls like changing clothes
你把人的靈魂 隨便像換裝娃娃一樣換來換去…
human life
因為人的生命
is just like toys and dolls.
就和玩具與人偶一樣
This guy is really dangerous.
這傢伙果然很危險
He truly regards
這傢伙是真的
human life as a plaything.
將人類的生命視為玩物
I absolutely cannot let my guard down.
我絕對不能放鬆警惕
Next, in order to live a peaceful life,
接下來 為了過上安穩的生活
I need to earn money quickly.
我得快點賺錢才行
Are there any jobs I can do
在這邊的世界裡 有我能做的工作嗎
You could kill people or rob them on the road.
你可以靠殺人 或是攔路搶劫什麼的去賺錢啊
I'm not very good at assassination.
我不是很擅長暗殺
Since you can kill me,
你都能把我殺掉了
killing people shouldn't be difficult for you.
那麼殺人對你來說應該不是件難事
I see.
原來如此
Don't be misled by her.
你別被她給帶偏了啊
A guest has arrived,
有客人上門了
probably looking for Misaki.
大概是來找美咲的
Huh? Looking for me?
什麼 找我的
You're the assassin Zaki, right?
妳就是殺手“咲”吧
If I don't do something,
再這樣下去的話
I'll be killed by a foreign assassin.
我就要被外國來的殺手給做掉了
Can you help me?
妳能幫幫我嗎
What should we do?
該怎麼辦才好呢
I already have another job.
我現在有別的工作在身
Please, if you don't help me…
拜託了 要是妳不幫我的話
I understand.
我明白了
I accept this commission.
這個委託我接了
Hey kid, did you hear our conversation just now?
喂 小鬼 你聽到我們剛才的對話了 對吧
Okay, since Polka said it's okay,
好 既然波爾卡都說可以了
I'll take on your commission.
我就接下你的委託吧
What is that guy
那傢伙
plotting?
到底在盤算著什麼
According to the intelligence dealer,
根據情報販子的消息
they should all be asleep in the inner part.
他們應該都睡在最裡面的那邊
These assassins
這些殺手們真是粗心大意啊
They were the partners of Jimba that you killed.
他們是之前被妳幹掉的那個 名叫陣場的殺手的夥伴
Rather than calling them assassins,
不過 與其說他們是殺手
it's more accurate to say they are a group of abnormal guys
不如說他們是一群 將目標的一家給滅門的
who wiped out an entire family of their target.
腦袋不正常的傢伙們
That uncle…
原來是那個大叔的夥伴啊
There was an ambush.
有埋伏
What kind of killers are you?
怎麼 身為殺手
You're too weak.
你們未免也太弱了吧
Because we're not assassins.
我們本來就不是殺手啊
Even so, our boss was killed by you.
儘管如此 畢竟我們的老大被妳給幹掉了
It's really embarrassing for us.
我們面子上實在是過不去啊
Hey, send her on her way.
喂 你們去送她上路
Oh, I see now.
嗯 這樣啊 我明白了
You little brat followed us too?
你這小鬼也跟過來了嗎
I'll take on
你們的委託
your commission.
就由我接下了
What did you say?
啊 你說什麼
You should disappear with Zaki too!
你也和“咲”一起消失吧
By the way, I forgot to tell you that
對了 我忘記告訴你們了
Misaki has already turned into a zombie.
美咲她已經變成殭屍了
A small injury won't kill her.
所以這點小傷是沒辦法殺死她的
She should be much stronger than before.
她應該變得比以前結實了不少
What… You bastard!
你 你這混蛋到底是什麼玩意啊
Can you hear me, Polka?
你能聽到嗎 波爾卡
Well,
那個 這時候是不是
should I say "hello" at this point?
要說“喂喂”啊
Did you know it was a trap beforehand?
你原本就知道這是陷阱了嗎
No,
不是的
I just accepted
我只是接受了委託
the commission
我接受了那些跟著這傢伙的
from children that followed this guy.
孩子們的委託
Amazing!
啊哈哈 好棒好棒
What is this? It's so interesting.
這是什麼 好有趣
What… What's going on?
這 這是 什麼情況
Let go of me, you bunch of brats.
你們這群小鬼 快放開我
They can no longer harm anyone,
他們再也無法殺害別人了
whether it's your father or mother.
無論是你們的父親還是母親
Mom… Dad…
媽媽 爸爸
Sorry,
抱歉
this isn't just about saving them.
我這並不是在拯救你們
Part of it is me venting my emotions,
多半只是我在發洩而已
so
所以
I don't need any reward.
我不需要報酬
I have really healed from where I was shot.
我被槍給擊中的地方真的已經癒合了
I have truly become
我真的變成了
But it seems like I've become duller.
不過我感覺我似乎變遲鈍了
It's the first time someone shot me from behind.
我還是頭一次被人從背後開槍命中
Do girls in this world just casually take off their clothes?
這個世界裡的女孩 都會若無其事地脫衣服嗎
Polka,
喂 波爾卡
why do you want to help those deceased children
你為什麼要幫 那些死去的孩子實現願望
Isn't life just a toy for you?
對你來說生命不都是玩具嗎
It's true that ultimately human life
沒錯 人類的生命說到底
is someone's toy.
終究都是某人的玩具
But I like toys
但是我喜歡玩具
because they can make children laugh.
因為玩具能夠讓孩子們笑出來
So how could I not value it?
所以我怎麼可能不去重視生命
I can never leave such a precious toy
我絕不能把如此寶貴的玩具
to those who make children suffer from the tragic fate.
留給那些給孩子們帶來 悲慘命運的傢伙們
Is that so?
是嗎 這樣啊
This guy's different values
原來這傢伙在價值觀上 跟我們最為不同的
are not about his attitude towards life,
並非是對“生命”的態度
but rather his understanding of toys?
而是對“玩具”的認知嗎
No wonder I can't agree with him.
怪不得我跟他說不到一起去
Polka can indeed be considered a dangerous person.
波爾卡的確可以算是危險人物
I don't care. This time you must die.
不管了 這次你一定要死掉喔
If you hadn't died, the disposal agency,
要是你沒死掉的話 我們“回收站”
wouldn't be able to get paid.
可就拿不到報酬了
Misaki and I
不過 要論混蛋程度的話
are probably behaving more badly than him.
大概還是我和美咲更勝一籌吧
Oh, sorry about what I said.
啊 抱歉 我的措辭不太好
You don't have to be so polite with me.
不用對我這麼客氣
If we count your past life,
包括你的前世在內
you should be older than me.
你的年紀應該比我大吧
That's how things are. It's really troublesome.
事情就是這樣 真的很麻煩啊
Is that so? Thanks, Kuruya.
是嗎 謝了 匠
Huh? I really don't plan to take on
嗯 我這邊是真的不打算 再承接殺掉四乃山波爾卡的委託了
And I really hate
而且我很討厭那幫傢伙居高臨下的態度
As for those who escaped today,
至於今天逃掉的那些人
I don't think we need to worry about them.
我認為我們沒有必要去擔心他們
They seem to have
畢竟他們貌似有點樹敵過多了
Damn it, I will definitely not spare
可惡 我絕對饒不了他
that monster.
那個怪物
Take all the weapons in the warehouse.
把倉庫裡的武器全都給我拿上
What's going on?
這 這是怎麼回事
Could it be done by the monster just now…?
難道是剛才那個怪物 事先斷了我們的後路嗎
Hey, don't joke around at a time like this.
喂 這種時候你就別開玩笑了
Lemmings…
旅…鼠…軍…團…
No way. Isn't that just
騙人的吧 那不只是
a legendary one?
傳說中的存在嗎
In this world,
在這邊的世界裡
are vampires also just legendary creatures?
就連吸血鬼也算是傳說中的存在嗎
Hey hey, do you have them over there?
喂喂 你們那裡真的有吸血鬼嗎
That's great.
好好喔
Vampires are very cool.
吸血鬼可是很帥的
If you have magic,
只要有魔力
perhaps you will evolve
或許妳遲早也會
sooner or later.
進化的
Is that true?
你說的是真的嗎
It's really just like a game,
真的是說得跟遊戲一樣耶
is that a profession transfer?
他們是把這樣當作是轉職嗎
Although I'm not sure how long this game of playing
雖然我不清楚 這個怪物要和殭屍玩扮家家酒
with the monster and zombie will last,
玩到什麼時候
I'll just play along
不過 我就暫時陪他們玩一玩好了
It's a good distraction
正好 我覺得人生有點無聊了
Is that really okay, Clarissa?
那樣真的好嗎 克拉麗莎
What? Are you talking about Polka?
什麼 妳是說波爾卡的事嗎
Can I take it that your relationship with him
我可以把這理解為妳和他的關係
has become intimate enough to call him Polka?
已經親暱到能用這樣的稱呼了嗎
He is very fond of children,
他很寵小孩子
so since he has this weakness,
既然他有這樣的弱點
I can easily control him.
我就能很輕鬆地駕馭他了
Aren't you also fond of children?
克拉麗莎 妳不也很寵小孩子嗎
Clarissa, you have a phone call.
克拉麗莎 有妳的電話
It's me.
是我
You really don't mind being bothered, do you?
你還真是不嫌煩啊
Polka Shinoyama is just a high school student, right?
你說四乃山波爾卡 只不過是一名高中生
Don't be ridiculous.
別開玩笑了
It's because I believed in such nonsense
就是因為我相信了你的這種鬼話
I would like to take a temporary break
我想暫時凍結和你們之間的關係
At least until Polka Shinoyama
至少四乃山波爾卡
dies once,
在死掉一次之前
and he is still just an ordinary high school student.
應該都還只是一名普通的高中生吧
That's hard to say.
這就不好說了
Right now the most important thing is
現在最重要的是
that we have one less troublesome client.
我們少了一位麻煩的客人
Alright, let's celebrate.
好了 我們來慶祝吧
This city has made my heart flutter after a long time.
這座城市久違地讓我心神蕩漾了起來
Be careful
選擇舞伴的時候 你要多加小心啊
Please…
拜 拜託你們了
I already apologized to you.
我不是已經向你們道過歉了嗎
I really don't have any money on me.
我身上真的沒帶錢
I didn't expect that a glass of beer
我沒想到一杯啤酒
would cost 60 000 yen.
居然就要價六萬日元
I heard that there are
我聽說這附近
more bars with extortionate charges around here again?
敲竹槓的酒吧又變多了
Hmm, it seems like one of those bars
嗯 我們隔壁大樓的四樓
is on the fourth floor of the nearby building.
貌似就是那種酒吧
Anyway, I can still drink good wine here
算了 反正這裡也能喝到好酒
and the prices are about the same.
而且價格也跟那邊差不多
By the way, where is Clarissa?
對了 克拉麗莎她人呢
She is working the night shift today
她今天上的是晚班
and will only come to work in the middle of the night.
她要到半夜才會過來
Is there something urgent
跟平常的上班時間不一樣啊 她是有急事嗎
or did something happen yesterday or today?
還是說她昨天或者今天發生了什麼事
Well,
這個嘛
there shouldn't be anything important.
她應該沒什麼要緊的事情吧
The fire that occurred at Shakuzawa Building yesterday
昨天酌澤大樓發生的那起火災
has been widely discussed in my workplace.
在我工作的地方可是傳得沸沸揚揚的
It is said that skeletons were seen,
說是有人看到了骨頭
but what's so scary about it?
這有什麼好可怕的啊
After all, don't all people turn into skeletons after they die?
所有人死後不都會變成骨頭嗎
They could also become
也有人死後 可能會屍蠟化或者變成木乃伊啊
I prefer zombies.
我比較喜歡殭屍
I want to eat you alive.
我要活活吃掉妳喔
Eliminate zombies… Smash their heads…
我要…消滅殭屍…把你的頭…打爛
It is forbidden to touch the waitress here.
我們這裡是禁止觸摸服務生的
But what will happen to
不過 殭屍啊
Misaki's body after she turned into a zombie?
美咲的身體會變成什麼樣啊
It hasn't been long
距她被槍擊中後還沒過多少時間吧
Due to the effect of preventing decay
因為有防止腐敗和肉體修復的效果
and repairing bodies, she won't be affected much.
所以她並不會怎麼樣的
It's just that she has more strength than before
她可能只是力氣變得比以前更大
and she may feel a little dull.
以及感覺變遲鈍了一點
If she suffers serious injuries,
如果她受了很重的傷
she can recover by eating raw meat.
只要吃點生肉 她就能夠恢復
That's what we call a carnivorous girl?
這就是所謂的肉食系女孩嗎
Sounds cool.
好棒 聽起來真酷
Is that so?
哪裡酷了
Additionally,
另外
her saliva should have a strong paralyzing effect.
她的唾液應該具有很強的麻痺效果
I feel like my saliva tastes sweeter than before.
我覺得我的唾液好像比之前更甜了
One bite from her can temporarily paralyze the opponent.
只要她咬上一口 就能讓對方陷入暫時麻痺的狀態
Polka!
波爾卡…
It's true.
真的耶
Look at you!
妳感嘆個屁啊
Do you want to try getting bit by me as well, Kuruya?
匠匠 你也要試試被人家咬一口嗎
This is a light bite from a girl.
這可是女孩子的輕咬喔
It's like a kiss, so you should feel happy about it.
是女孩子的親親喔 你應該會覺得很高興吧
Shut up, materialistic woman!
閉嘴 妳這個三次元
Materialistic woman!
三次元
I am the kind of man
我可是那種能夠對“自己的親吻
who can firmly say no
對所有男性來說都是獎賞”
who believe their kiss
抱有這種想法的自我意識過剩的女性
is a reward for all men.
果斷地說不的男人
This kind of woman is just like the man
這種女人就和初次見面
who say things like, "As a reward for meeting you, I'll make you my woman"
嘴裡就碎念著“作為獎賞 就讓妳成為我的女人吧”的
right off the bat.
這一類的男人如出一轍
Kuruya.
匠匠
You are a monster born
你這個現代社會孕育而出的
in this modern society.
怪物
Speaking of which, does such a monster exist in this world?
說起來 這個世界裡有那樣的存在嗎
A monster with exceptional power
類似“災厄殲滅者”的那種
like the Calamity Crusher.
超乎常理的怪物
Is it really the sound of gunfire?
真的是槍聲嗎
Not sure.
我也不清楚
Since someone reported it,
不過既然有人報警了
let's come and take a look.
我們還是過來巡邏一下吧
What's that sound?
什麼聲音
What's going on with these people?
這些人是怎麼回事
So
所以
I already apologized
我不是都已經向你們低頭道歉了嗎
Why are people calling me now?
他怎麼這時候打來啊
I could have seen Clarissa
明明再過一會
in just a little while.
我就能見到克拉麗莎了
It's really regrettable.
真的讓我很遺憾啊
By the way,
對了
is the world of Polka also based on decimal system?
波爾卡的世界裡也是用十進位的嗎
Yes.
沒錯
That means humans there also have ten fingers.
也就是說 你們那邊人類的手指也是十根囉
Well,
這個嘛
although there are individual differences,
雖然存在個體差異
most people have ten fingers.
但大多數人都是十根手指
You are guessing they use the decimal system
因為有十根手指 所以用的是十進位
just because they have ten fingers, right?
你這只能算是一種猜測吧
It's surprising that you know these things.
虧你還懂得這些啊
Speaking of which, even though it's a different world,
話說 明明是異世界
human bodies are surprisingly similar to this extent.
可人類的軀體居然相似到這種地步
Additionally, can the magic from the other world
是說 異世界的魔法
have the same effect here?
在這邊能起到相同的作用嗎
It seems so.
貌似是可以的
The world I once stayed in and this world
我曾待過的那個世界和這邊的世界
may be connected somewhere.
也許在某處是存在關聯的
Otherwise,
若非如此
many things wouldn't make sense.
很多事便說不通了
Have you finally recovered from the numbness?
你終於從麻痺的狀態恢復過來了嗎
Hmm.
嗯
Now I have another skill of biting people in the future.
今後我又多了一項咬人的技能呢
Why don't you just beat them?
妳直接動手不是能更快見效嗎
I want to use this move to immobilize my opponent.
我要用這招讓對方無法動彈
Before, I used a nail gun to pin them down on the ground,
我以前都是用釘槍 把對方給釘在地上的
but now I can save so many nails.
這下我就能節省好多釘子了
It is also an environmentally-friendly move.
妳還真是環保啊
That's right. The more ways there are
沒錯 這種能夠讓對方 失去行動能力的手段
to immobilize the opponents, the better.
是越多越好的
You seem to have quite a few means like that.
那樣的手段你貌似有不少吧
For example, you buried those hooligans in the ground and even
比方說 你將那幫小混混都埋進了土裡的那個
saved trouble of dealing with their bodies, which is quite convenient.
這樣連處理屍體的工夫都省了 倒是挺方便的
Huh? Those people are still alive.
沒有啊 那些人都還是活著的
But they have lost their sanity
不過他們已經失去了理智
and probably cannot provide testimony anymore.
應該是沒法提供證言了
You're too impulsive.
你這也太隨便了吧
Don't worry.
別擔心
In order to avoid accidentally killing people again,
為了讓他們不能再殺人 我有好好注意
Mr. Iwa, there's a strong smell of alcohol on you.
你身上的酒味好重啊 岩先生
It's much better than the smell of blood on you.
比你身上有血腥味好多了
How did you get covered in blood like that?
你怎麼搞得一身都是血
This was self-defense and I already apologized to them.
我這可是正當防衛 而且我明明就已經向他們道過歉了
I thought they were going to kill me instead.
我還以為自己會被那幫人殺掉
To be killed?
你這傢伙被殺掉
So what's the matter?
所以 這是什麼情況
I see.
原來如此
Given this situation…
看這情況 怪不得啊
It's my first time
我還是頭一次見到
seeing human bodies tied up like this.
把人的身體給打結的
No wonder the Mobile Investigation Team called us
難怪機搜再進行初次搜查前
before conducting their initial search.
就把我們叫過來了
As expected, this kind of thing falls within our jurisdiction.
這種事情果然處於我們的管轄範圍嗎
For this kind of supernatural event,
對於這種超自然事件
no other department is an expert.
無論哪個部門都是門外漢
In the end, we still have to do the work.
說來說去 不都還是得我們幹活嗎
Lemmings,
“旅鼠軍團”
Grim Reaper,
“死神”
Fire-breathing Bug,
“赴火之蟲”
and after those guys, another calamity has emerged.
繼那些傢伙之後 又冒出了一個“災厄”啊
It really makes people excited.
真是讓我熱血沸騰啊
TSUBAKI IWANOME, THE MANAGER OF SHINJUKU POLICE'S COMMUNITY SAFETY DIVISION MATERIALS COMPILING GROUP #3
(新宿警察局生活安全科第三資料編輯係 係長) (岩野目椿)
KOZABURO ARASE, IN THE SAME DEPARTMENT
(同係所属 荒瀨耿三郎)
We will be busy.
這下警察叔叔可有得忙囉
(Episode 4: The Mad Dog)
(第4集 The Mad Dog -狂犬-)